

# Kevin Kloosterman

Data Analyst
With Digital Power since September 2024



- +31 (0) 6 3078 4428
- kevin.kloosterman@digital-power.com
- in Linkedin.com/in/kevinkloosterman
- kevinkloosterman.github.io / github.com/kevinkloosterman

#### **About Kevin**

Kevin is an all-round data specialist with experience in technical data solutions as well as the applied fields of data analytics. Having worked a lot with tools like Looker Studio, BigQuery, GA4, and GTM, he knows his way around a dataset and understand the processes that formed it. In his spare time, he likes to use python, html, css, and js to develop his own tools and apps of interest.

#### Core qualities

Solution Oriented

#### Work experience

#### **Data Analyst**

**Digital Power** Sep 2024 – present

#### **Data Consultant**

Netprofiler Nov 2023 – Aug 2024 In my current position, I primarily:

- · Perform data visualization and analysis
- Advise clients on how to turn their data into actionable insights

### As a Data Consultant at Netprofiler, it was my job to:

- Design and implement tracking solutions
- Extract information from dataLayer objects
- Build intuitive dashboards
- Process raw data
- Perform performance analysis
- Lead Consent Mode v2 implementation project for all clients
- Configure and maintain GTM containers
- Automate workflows with Python
- Advise on data solutions
- Host KPI sessions

#### SEA & Data Consultant

Netprofiler

Jan 2023 – Nov 2023

As an SEA & Data Consultant at Netprofiler, it was my job to:

- Build intuitive dashboards
- Implement tracking tags
- Extract information from dataLayer objects
- Debug tracking anomalies
- Manage PPC campaigns
- Perform PPC performance analysis

## **Digital Marketeer**

Cadform

Sep 2020 – Dec 2022

As a Digital Marketeer at Cadform, it was my job to:

- Design and implement tracking solutions
- Configure and maintain GTM
- Build intuitive dashboards
- Perform marketing performance analysis
- Perform CRO analysis
- Manage PPC marketing
- Manage social media marketing
- Manage email marketing

**Education** 

Media, Information, and Communication

Minors

Neuromarketing



**Hogeschool van Amsterdam** 2017 – 2021 Digital Marketing

Thesis

"To what extent should De Consumentenbond inform and advise consumers about neuromarketing within e-commerce platforms to contribute to its ethical correctness?"

Languages	<b>Dutch</b>	<b>English</b>	<b>ltalian</b>	<b>Spanish</b>
	Mother tongue	Fluent	Basic	Basic
Tools & Methods	Tools  Looker Studio Google Analytics 4 Google Tag Manager Google BigQuery Chrome Devtools Github		Methods  Python Pandas  Matplotlib SQL Javascript Google Apps Scripts	

